Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Statement on Behalf of Bethlehem Steel Company and Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Carroll Daugherty; David Cole; Samuel Rosenman. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Steelworkers' Case for Wages, Pensions and Social Insurance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Should the Steel Wage Recommendation be Accepted?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Robert Nathan; Jules Backman; Henry Hazlitt; Stanley Ruttenberg; Malcom Sharp. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Steel Wage Issue, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By American Metal Market. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Statement before the Presidential Board in the Matter of United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Statement of A. B. Homer, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By carroll Daugherty; David Cole. In the Matter of the Issues Under te Reopening Provisions of Agreements Berween United Steelworkers of America and Bethlehem Steel Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industry's Review, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By richars Bennett. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Statement for New Determination Under the Walsh-Healey Act of the Prevailing Minimm Wages, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: The Recent Steel Price Increases, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Wages--Prices--Profits, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Post-War Wage Determination in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Albert rees. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the 1944 Fall Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Minutes. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minutes of the 1944 Spring Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Suggestion Systems - A Selected List of References, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Society of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: An Employee Suggestion System for the Small Plant or Store, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Donald Wilhelm Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Suggestion Plans for Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A Simple Way to have a Successful Employee Suggestion System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Personnel Materials Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Statistical Report for the Year 1954, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Asociation of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Cashing in on Ideas, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Merchants and Manudacturers Association. A tool for increasing job interes. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What Employees Think of Suggestions Plans, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By robert Gray. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Evaluating Intangible Suggestions, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Suggestion Sustems. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Statistical report for the Year 1955, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Minites of the Spring 1943 Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. May 19, 20 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Fall 1943 Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. November 3,4, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Story of United's Employees Suggestion Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By War Oroduction Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By US War Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Production Drive, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By US War Production Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Plans for Stimulating Suggestions from Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Beatrice Brower. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Suggestions from Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Suggestion Sustems Adoptd in Force by Industrial and Other Business Organizations, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Industrial Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Industrial relations Counselors. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Successful Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Annual Statistical Report for the Year 1957, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: National Association of Duggestion Systems Presented at the Chicago Convention, October 29-30, 1956, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By American Cyanamid Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Objectives of a Suggestion System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Eligibility of Suggesters, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Administration of a Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1959, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1958, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Report on the Study of Adoption and Non Adoption Letters, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Suggestion Boxes, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Annual Satistical report for the Year 1956, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The Syndical Corporative System in Italy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: A Guide to Promotion and Publicity for an Effective incentive Awards Program, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Anonymous, Partially and Fully Identified Suggestion plans, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1963, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1960, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Annual Statistical Report for the Year 1961, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1962, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Starting a Suggestion System in your Organization, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1965, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Proceedings of the 24th Annual Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. October 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Suggestion Scheme: a Contribution to Morale or an Economic Transction?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By C. C. Gorfin. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Teaching Salaries then and Now, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Beardsley Ruml; Sidney Tickton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Occasional Papers from the Aft Program for Quality Educational Standards in Teaching, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Quest report on Differentiated Staffing, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of research. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Conceptual Framework for Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Occasional Papers from QUEST, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Occational Papers from QUEST, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Grievance Procedures for Teachers in Negotiation Agreements, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By research Division. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Occasional papers from QUEST, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By Department of Research. No. 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Role of Collective Bargaining in Public Education, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By National PTA. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Technology and the Great American Experiment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Technological Disemployment in the Coal Industry, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Walker Polakov. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report on Hearings by the Committee and Summary by Dewey Anderson, Executive Secretary, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Technology and the Concentration of Economic Power, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Theodore Kreps. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends in Technology and Employment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Primary Employment Effects of Productivity Gains, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Eric Schiff. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Unemployment and Defense, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By American Association for Adult Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Author Index to Industrial Change and Employment Opportunity - A Selected Bibliography, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By F. C. Harrington; Corrington Gill. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Trade-Union Policy and Technological Change, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By National Research Project. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Final Statement at the Closing Public Session to Consider Recommendations, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Joseph O' Mahoney. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Sharing the Gains of Technological Change, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Clyde Denkert. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Summary of Current Technological Development Division, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Men Steel and Technocal Change, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Department of Scientific and Industrial Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Management and Technology, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Speeding up the Workers, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By James Bernett. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Machinery and the American Standard of Living, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Machinery and Allied Proucts Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Technology and the American Consumer, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Machinery and Allied Products Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Job Ahead for Machinery, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Allen Rucker; N. W. Pickering. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Costs and American Democracy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Thomas Jefferson Wertenbaker. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Technology and Planning, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By National resources Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Machines and Tomorrow's World, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By William Ogburn. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: You and Machines, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Ecnonomics of Technocracy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Harry Gideonse. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Machinery's Part in Future Social Progress, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Productivity as a Remedy for Inflation, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Labor, Machines and Depressions, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: A Pictorial Presentation of Facts on Mechanization, Working Hours and the American Standad of Living, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Ten Facts on Technology and Employment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: More Facts on Technology and Employment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Report on the Effect of the Development of the machine on Employment and Standard of Living, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Fact Finding Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Technological Unemployment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By paul Douglas. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Technology and the Mineral Industries, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By National research Project and Bureau of Mines. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Mechanization Trends in Metal and Nonmetal Mining as Indicated by Sales of Underground Loading Equipment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    By Harry Hopkins; Corrington Gill. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Systems of Shop Management in the Cotton-Garment Industry, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Adjusting to Automation, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Worker in the New Industrial Environment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By Foundation Research on Human Behavior. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Work Force Adjustments to Technological Change, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By Bureau of Employment Security. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Manpower Adjustments to Automation and Technological Change in Western Europe, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Technological Change & Employment in the Automotive Industry, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By Garth Magnum. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Microelectronics and Employment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Technological Change and Unions, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By Dennis Chamot. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Microtechnology, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By National Union of Provincial Government Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Automationand Womens Workers, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By Wage and Labor Standards Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Silicon, Satellites and Robots, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By Dennis Chamot; Joan Baggett. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Inegration Movement in the Southern Textile Industry and its regional, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Taft-Hartlyism in Textiles, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Displaced textile Worker A Case Study, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By research and Statistics Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Air Conditioning in Textile Mills, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Research Department Technical Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Analysis of 31 Southern Labor Contracts, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Henry Mims; Guy Arthur Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Picture Story of the Cotton Textile Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Textile Information Servce. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Story of the Cotton Textile Workers, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Ten years of Work Experience of Philadelphia eavers and Loom Fixers, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Gladys Palmer; Kate Edelman; Eileen Leach; helen Klopfer. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Hosiery Industry and the National Economy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Health and Welfare Funds in the Needle Trades, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Adolph Held. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Forty-cent Minimum Wage for the Women's Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Lazare Teper. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Development of Unionism in the Clothing Industries, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Robert Goold. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Conspiracy in Southern Textiles, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    By William Pollock. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: This is the Real J.P. Stevens, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The U.S. Textile Industry: Its Importance, Its Future, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    By Du Pont Context. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Earnings and Hours in the Finishing of Wool Textiles and all Textiles, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. 1933-34. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Why This Strike, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Julius Hochman. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Hourly and Weekly Earnings in Textile Dyeing and Finishing: Cotton, Silk, and Rayon, 1933 and 1934, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Southern Labor in Revolt, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Kenneth Meiklejohn; Peter Nehemkis. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Report on the Conditions and Problems of the Cotton Textile Industry, Made by the Cabinet Committee, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Message from the President of the United States. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Economic Development of the Cotton-Textile Industry in the United States, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Emily Day; Rachel Lane. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Report of the Chairman of the Woven Label Fact Finding Committee, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Textile and Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Earnings of Cotton Mill Operatives, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Robert layer. 1825 - 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Employment Changes in Textile Mill Products, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Department of Employment Security. 1939 - 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Wage Determination no. 55 for the Textile Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Union of South Africa, Wage Board. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Job Instruction, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    By Bureau of Training. Sessions Outline and Reference Material. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the 5th Annual Conference of the Training Within Industry Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    By Training within Industry Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Proceedings of the 4th Conference of the Training Within Industry Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Infringements of Trade Union Rights in Southern Africa, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Teamsters Union on the West Coast, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By J. B. Gillingham. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining in the Trucking Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Executive committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining in the Trucking Industry 1962, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Policy Recommendations of the Executive Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Training Problems in War-Production Plants and How they were Overcome, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Bureau of Training. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Faster Mail for Less Money, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Sixth Annual Time Study and Methods Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Conference Proceedings. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Eighth Annual Time Study and Methods Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Proceedings of the Fifth Annual Time Study and Methods Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Proceedings for the Seventh Annual Time Study and Methods Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor's Attitude Toward Scientific Management, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Union Attitudes Toward Predetermined Motion Time Systems, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    By Bertram Gottlieb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Understanding Time Study, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    By William O. Kuhl. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Women in the Trade Union Movement, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Two Centuries of Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Address of the President, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    By Anne Godwin. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What the TUC is Doing, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    By Sir Vincent Tewson. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Productivity, Prices and Incomes, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    By Report of theExecutive Committees. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The TUC: A Plan for the 1970s, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    By John Hughes. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Investigation of Strikes, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Production and Industrial Development, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    By Trades Union Congress Report 1955. Excerpts from the Proceedings. Item is in English.
- Box 25, Folder (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Problem of Unemployment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Building for Recovery, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Harold Ickes. The Story of PWA. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Unemployment - and its Remedies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Disadvantaged Youth on the Labor Market, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Division of Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Balancing Production and Employment through Management Control, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Department of Manufacture. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Area of Agreement at the 4th Fortune Round Table, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Job Instruction, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    A Manual for Shop Supervisors and Instructors. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Training Womanpower, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Seasonal Employment in Agriculture, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Benjamin Free. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Structure of the American Economy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Gardiner Means; D. E. Montgomery; J. M. Clark; Alvin H. Hansen; Mordecai Ezekiel. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Training Within Industry Material, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Office of Production management. Volume 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Training Within Industry Materials, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Volume 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Training Within Industry Materials, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Training Within Industry Bulletins, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Andrei Verbin, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    By Soviet Trade Unions. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The "Illiberal" Education of Society Managers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: American and Soviet Economy: Contrast and Comparison, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Foreign Labor Information, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Foreign Labor Information, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Management in the Soviet Union, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Guide to War Labor Board Policy, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    By Sidney Podolsky. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What it is How it Operates, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    By Division of Public Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Obtaining Approval from the National War Labor Board of Voluntary Wage Agreements and Wage Adjustments, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    By Handbook. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Disputes Before the War Labor Board, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Directive Orders and Opinions of the National War Labor Board in the "Little Steel" Case, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)